<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@color/colorPrimary"
    android:padding="20dp"
    >

        <LinearLayout android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical"
            android:background="@color/colorPrimary"
            android:paddingBottom="50dp">
            <TextView android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:text="TERMS OF USE"
                android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"
                android:textSize="40dp"/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/termsofuse1"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:text="1.Users may kindly note that products listed on our app are sourced from our own inventory, through our brand partners and Contributors (i.e. users who list outfits owned by them on App (as defined hereinafter) for lease).
This document is published in accordance with the provisions of Rule 3 (1) of the Information Technology (Intermediaries Guidelines) Rules, 2011 that require publishing the rules and regulations, privacy policy and Terms of Use for access or usage of the Mobile Application https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.rentit.android&amp;hl=en (hereinafter referred to as the “App”) and the website http://www.rentit.com (hereinafter referred to as the “website”). This electric record is generated by a mobile phone and does not require any physical or digital signatures. "
                />
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/termsofuse2"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:text="2.The domain name http://www.rentit.com (hereinafter referred to as the ) and
                the App https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.rentit.androidamp;hl=en is owned by RentIt Private Limited, a company incorporated under the Companies Act, 2013 having its registered office at Collector Colony,Chembur East, Mumbai -400058. "
                />
            <TextView android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="USER ELIDGIBILITY"
                android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"
                android:textSize="25dp"/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/userelidgibility1"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="1.For the purpose of these Terms of Use and including the applicable policies which are herein by way of reference, wherever the context so requires “App User User” or “he/ she” or “his/ her” shall mean any natural or legal person who is competent to enter into a legally binding Contract under the “Indian Contract Act, 1872” (hereinafter referred to as the “Contract Act”). Any person who is not competent under the Contract Act to enter into a legally binding Contract including minors, un- discharged insolvents, persons of unsound mind etc are not eligible to use this App and website. This App and website is intended for individuals who are 18 years of age or above. By accessing or using this App and website or the services rendered by this App and website in any manner, the App User and the Website User warrants that he/ she is 18 years of age or above.
            " />
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/userelidgibility2"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:text="2.Items rendered for sale/ hire on this App and Website may be used and worn by individuals who are below 18 years of age, but, rentals and all other payments should necessarily be made by persons who are 18 years of age or above. If a Minor (person below 18 years of age) wishes to use or transact on this App and Webite, such use or transaction shall be made by his/ her legal guardian or parents on this App and Website. The App Owner / Website Owner reserves the right to terminate the membership and/ or refuse to provide the App User / Website User with access to this App / Website if it is brought to App Owner's / Website Owner’s notice or if it is discovered that the App User / Website User is under the age of 18 years or is incompetent to enter into a legally binding Contract according to the provisions of the Contract Act. "
                />
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/userelidgibility3"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:text="The parties to this agreement are the lessor and the lessee where RentIt or RentIt Pvt Ltd. Or the company is the Lessor and the customer who wishes to rent the apparel or accessory (either western wear or ethnic wear) is the lessee or “you”. By renting any apparel or accessory on Flyrobe.com or the Mobile Apps owned by Flyrobe you agree to be bound by these general terms and conditions of the company. The terms of the rental agreement are as follows: "
                />
            <TextView android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="NATURE OF CONTRACT"
                android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
                android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:textSize="25dp"/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/natureofcontract1"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:text="Here the rights to use the product are transferred to you on payment of the rent to RentIt and thus you are the deemed owner of the usage rights of the good.
                In no way this contract signifies that the good belongs to you on a permanent basis, the same have to be returned in a condition similar to the condition in which it was delivered to you. As per the MVAT Act, this is transfer of usage rights to you."
                />
            <TextView android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="TETURE OF CONTRACT"
                android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
                android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:textSize="25dp"/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/tetureofcontract1"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:text="Contract has a period that is equivalent to the tenure of the contract that has been chosen by the customer while placing the order. The return date is fixed and is imprinted on the proforma invoice, the apparel / accessory has to be returned in as-is condition, by the return date, as was delivered to the customer by RentIt."/>
            <TextView android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="USER ACCOUNT REGISTRATION"
                android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
                android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:textSize="25dp"/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/useraccountregstration1"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:text="The App User / Website may need not register himself/ herself to navigate through this App / Website, but, is required to register himself/ herself on this App/Website by making an Account on this App/Website, called as the “RentIt Account” for availing all/some of the services provided by this App/ Website, including, but not limited to renting of the products available on this App / Website. The App User / Website user shall be allowed to rent the products displayed on this App / Website or avail any of the services provided by this App / Website, only after registering himself/ herself on this App / Website. App User/ Website User shall maintain the privacy and confidentiality of the information provided by him/ her for registering himself/ herself on this App / Website called the “Account Information” including, but not limited to the Display Name and the Password. The App User / Website User shall be solely liable and responsible for the correctness of the Account Information being provided by him/ her. "/>

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/useraccountregstration2"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:text="The App/Website User’s relationship with the Third Party Service Provider associated with the App /Website User’s Third Party Account on the applicable social networking site(s) is solely governed by the App /Website User’s agreement(s) with such Third Party Service Provider. The App /Website Owner does not review any of the information provided by the App/Website User to such Third Party Account on the applicable social networking sites for any purpose, including, but not limited to, for accuracy, legality or non-infringement and the App/Website Owner is not responsible for any information which the App/Website Owner uses from the Third Party Account.
              The App /Website User agrees that if the App/Website User provides any information which is inaccurate, not current or incomplete or where the App/Website Owner has reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, or not in accordance with the Terms of Use of this App /Website then the App/Website Owner shall have the right to indefinitely suspend or terminate or block access to membership of the App/Website User on this App /Website and refuse the App/Website User access to this App/Website, without assigning any reason(s), thereof. "/>

            <TextView android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="PAYMENT POLICY"
                android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
                android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:textSize="25dp"/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/paymentpolicy1"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:text="he refundable deposit, if any, has to be paid in full while accepting the delivery for the placed order. The affiliates of RentIt completing the delivery will hand over a proforma invoice with the payment details chosen by the customer. The invoice / receipt would be mailed to you electronically on successful completion of the order.

                 There are no charges for delivery and pick-up, However Flyrobe may start charging for the extra service at any point in future. The deposit, if any, is a refundable and interest free amount, billed to you at the time of delivery or at the time of confirming the order online and will be subject to refund only post successful verification of the quality of the apparel returned to Flyrobe.

                The deposit, partially or in full, may be retained if the apparel is damaged beyond repair i.e. can’t be repaired or the cost of repairs being very high."></TextView>
            <TextView android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="DAMAGE POLICY"
                android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
                android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:textSize="25dp"/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/damage1"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:text="The Lessee agrees to pay for any damage to, loss of, or any theft (disappearance) of apparel/accessory , regardless of cause or fault.

                Minor wear and tear is accepted and will be ignored, on consideration and acceptance by Flyrobe.

                Any damage that results in the product being unusable will result in the deposit amount being charged to the lessee.

                Stains on apparel/accessory which are not removable via dry cleaning / cleaning will result in deposit amount being charged to the lessee. The extent of damage would be ascertained by comparing against the apparel as was delivered to you by Flyrobe. Any variation showing damages, if ascertained as not caused by normal wear and tear, would result in the deposit being retained."/>

            <TextView android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="DISCLAIMER"
                android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
                android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"
                android:textSize="25dp"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/disclaimer"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="@color/colorwhite"
                android:text="The App /Website Owner does not guarantee that the App/Website User will always have an uninterrupted access to this App/Website and it does not warrant that the information available on this App/Website is complete, true, accurate and not misleading. Nothing on this App/Website constitutes or is meant to constitute advice of any kind. The App /Website Owner will make their best effort to provide an error free and continuously available App/Website without any dangerous elements being sent to the App/Website User’s computer, laptop, mobile phone or any other device with which he/ she is using this App/Website. However, the App /Website Owner shall not be liable to the App/Website User in any way, in relation to the content, use, electronic communication sent or otherwise anything in connection with this App/Website is free from viruses or other harmful components. The App/Website Owner cannot fully control the internet’s flow of information, it cannot ensure that they do not contain any elements that may harm the App/Website User’s computer, laptop, mobile phone or any other device with which the App/Website User is using this App/Website.

                The App/Website Owner may, at its own discretion, at any time without any prior notice, take steps to ensure the security and quality of this App /Website and restrict or limit the access to this App/Website.

                RentIt is not affiliated with, endorsed or sponsored by the trademark holders of the product. The trademarks are used on the website to identify products of the respective trademark holders and to inform the customers of their source."></TextView>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
